Callaghan Swearengen

| calswear@gmail.com | Marina del Rey, CALIFORNIA

Summary

Cal is a brand specialist with a passion for digital marketing. He excels in copywriting, user-experience, and multimedia - as evidenced by his work with MBC Strategic. He is a friendly, motivated, passionate and always willing to go the extra mile. Check out his portfolio at https://calswear.myportfolio.com/

Experience

MBC Strategic | Santa Monica, CA Digital Strategist | 04/2022 - 01/2023

- Performed key roles in developing brand strategy for 10+ corporate real estate and finance projects
- Worked closely with designers to develop insights reports, brand strategy decks, firm marketing materials, and websites
- Interfaced directly with client executives through multiple presentations as well as liaised between teams for delivery

Hoskin Capital | Marina del Rey, CA

Co-Founder/Business Development Specialist | 06/2020 - 03/2022

- Played a key role in building the company while passing his Series 65 in college
- Oversaw firm's brand development, social media content creation, marketing campaigns, and event planning
- · Directly influenced and coordinated \$100K in capital investments from outside investors
- Helped company raise \$1.6M in managed assets while overseeing 2 employees

Anne Alvarez Real Estate | San Francisco, CA Social Media Manager | 06/2021 - Present

- · Directly responsible for brand presentation online, while communicating with agent directly on a daily basis
- Channels include Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, & Twitter

Stricklin Development | San Francisco, CA Real Estate Development Intern | 06/2018 - 08/2018

Project management assistant, developing quality control assets and processes directly for CEO (reference available)

Education

CU Boulder | Boulder, CO

Communication, B.A., Media Production, Minor | 05/2021

College of Media, Communication, and Information - GPA: 3.8 (with Distinction)

UCLA Extension | Los Angeles, California Digital Marketing Certificate (04/2022 - Present)

Chapman University | Orange, CA Strategic & Corporate Communication

Skills

Copywriting, Microsoft Powerpoint, Microsoft Office, Digital Marketing, SEO, SEMRush, Google Analytics, Microsoft word, Microsoft excel, Real Estate, Finance, Institutional Branding, Communication, Leadership, Adobe Creative Suite

Work Abroad & Other Experience

Studied Entrepreneurship at London School of Economics (UK), French language at France Langue, Nice (FR), international business and Spanish at Suffolk University, Madrid (ES)